<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Urban on Arman</title>
    <link>https://armannd092.github.io/portfolio/urban/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Urban on Arman</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://armannd092.github.io/portfolio/urban/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Q-City</title>
      <link>https://armannd092.github.io/portfolio/q-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://armannd092.github.io/portfolio/q-city/</guid>
      <description>Q-city is a new experience of park in a super-city. It is trying to reactivate park as a public space by adding layers of gamification to it. This physical game tied to a digital app, which provide citizens with extensive information about their activity. Moreover, it allow users to pair with each other for more public interaction inside this space. Along with this primary objective, the games designed to produce electricity as a byproduct as a source for the park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New York Bike sharing system</title>
      <link>https://armannd092.github.io/portfolio/new-york-bike-sharing-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://armannd092.github.io/portfolio/new-york-bike-sharing-system/</guid>
      <description>Advisor : Diego , Areti Markopoulou
External link
 Number of trips in days of month different season.Number of trips in hours of days in different season.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Eye</title>
      <link>https://armannd092.github.io/portfolio/the-eye/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://armannd092.github.io/portfolio/the-eye/</guid>
      <description>The Eye is a single web platform which help the urban designer and decision maker to simulate and predict the impact of different urban planning scenarios. This platform uses real-time data through the computer algorithm and machine learning in order to transform the raw data to the knowledge about cities dynamic state. Furthermore, the project open up a new workflow for urban planning by providing a range of concussion that proposals will may cause.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>